Steward Jeyn is here!
Perfect.
- Steward Jeyn!
Who are these people?
Why do they
not kneel before me?
Steward Jeyn, someone has humiliated me.
Who?
Daring to insult someone chosen by the Sovereign Sanctum?！
Those two who refused to kneel. Them.
Who are they?
One is Elowen Morellan,
the
heir of the Morellan family.
The other is Severin Carter, a disowned son
and my former fiancé
who I just dumped.
You just dumped him?
Isn’t this supposed to
be your wedding ceremony?
It is.
But I changed grooms.
This is Redmond Carter,
the new heir of House Carter, my new fiancé.
Livia and I will
serve you faithfully, Steward Jeyn.
The Morellan family?
Correct.
The Morellan family may lead the Four Great Families,
but compared to the
Sovereign Sanctum, you are nothing.
Since this is your first offense,
kneel and apologize to me now,
and I’ll spare your family.
You…
Steward Jeyn, please.
My dear worthless brother, where did all that earlier arrogance go?
One look at Steward
Jeyn and you fold?
Enough.
No need to waste time
on these bottom-feeding insects.
Let’s proceed with the contract.
Partnership with the Sovereign Sanctum is what matters.
Of course, Steward Jeyn.
I have one condition.
to teach these insects a lesson.
Don’t worry.
I’ll issue a decree
from the Sovereign Sanctum later.
The Morellan patriarch will crawl to you
and apologize personally.
Thank you, Steward Jeyn.
What happened to all that arrogance?
And you, where did your big talk go?
Just wait.
Once I sign
with the Sovereign Sanctum,
all of Golantis
will answer to me.
You’ll spend the rest of
your life rotting in the mines.
Livia, stop wasting breath on ants.
Sign the contract.
With the Sovereign Sanctum’s support,
the Scott family will
shake all of Golantis!
Don’t bother.
You won’t be signing that contract.